let quiz   =[
    {question: "A-B is read as?",
option:[
    "Difference of A and B of B and A ",
    "Difference of B and A",
    "Difference of A and B",
    "None of these",

],
answer:1, 
},

{
    question: " If A,B and C are any three sets, then AX(B U C) is equal to" ,
option:[
    "(AXB) U (BXC)",
    "(A U B) X (A U C)",
    "(AXB) U (AXC)",
    "None of these",


],
answer : 3, 
},
{
    question: "Two functions f and g are said to be equal if f",
option:[
    "The domain of f = The domain of g",
    "The co-domain of f= The co-domain of g",
    "f(x)=g(x) for all x",
    "All of Above",


],
answer:4, 
},
{question: "Limit x->0 sin (ax)/bx is",
option:[
    0,
    1,
    "a/b",
    "b/a",

],
answer:3, 
},

{
    question: "The value of the limit x->0 {log(1+ax)}/x is ",
option:[
    "a",
    0,
    1,
    "1/a",

],
answer : 1, 
},
{
    question: "If f(x)= x sin(1/x),x is not equal to 0, then limit x-> 0 f(x) is",
option:[
    1,
    0,
    -1,
    "Does not exist",

],
answer:2, 
},
{
    question: "There are 12 points in a plane out of which 5 are collinear. The number of triangles formed by the points as vertices is",
option:[
    185,
    210,
    220,
    175,


],
answer : 2, 
},
{
    question: "Four dice are rolled. The number of possible outcomes in which at least one dice show 2 is " ,
option:[
    1296,
    625,
    585,
    671,


],
answer:4, 
},
{
    question: "The value of P(n,n-1) is",
option:[
    "n",
    "2n",
    "n!",
    "2n!",

],
answer : 3, 
},
{
    question: "The number of ways of painting the faces of a cube with six different colors is ",
option:[
    1,
    6,
    "6!",
    "None of these",

    
],
answer:1, 
},
{
    question: "The perpendicular distance from the point (3,-4) to the line 3x-4y+10=0",
option:[
    7,
    8,
    9,
    10,
    

],
answer : 1, 
},
{
    question: "If Mean=Median=Mode,then it is ",
option:[
    "Asymmetric disbution",
    "Symmetric disbution",
    "Both Symmetric disbution and Asymetric disbution",
    "None of these",

],
answer:2, 
},
{
    question: "If the difference of mode and median of a data is 24, then the difference of median and mean is",
option:[
    24,
    8,
    36,
    12,



],
answer : 4, 
},
{
    question: "Two cards from a pack of cards are lost. One card is drawn from the remaining cards. If drawn card is diamond then the probability that the lost cards were both hearts is",
option:[
    "143/1176",
    "143/11760",
    "143/11706",    
    "134/11760",

],
answer:2, 
},
{
    question: "If four whole numbers taken at random are multiplied together,then the chance that the last digit in the product is 1,3,5,7 is",
option:[
    "16/25",
    "16/125",
    "16/625",
    "None of these",

],
answer:3, 
}]